etsyrank.com 2019-06-15

# Privacy Policy

This following document sets forth the Privacy Policy for the eRank websites, [www.etsyrank.com](http://www.etsyrank.com/) and www.erank.com.

eRank is committed to providing you with the best possible customer service experience while safeguarding your privacy as well as your personal information.  We are committed to keeping your data secure and your personal information confidential

 **Collection of your personal information**

There are many aspects of the site which can be viewed without providing personal information, however, for access to some eRank features you are required to submit personally identifiable information. This information may include but is not limited to: email address(es), unique username(s) and password(s), or provide sensitive information in the recovery of your lost password.

 **Sharing of your personal information**

We may occasionally hire other companies or subcontract other providers to provide services on our behalf, including but not limited to handling customer support enquiries, processing transactions or customer freight shipping. Those companies will be permitted to obtain  the personal information they need to deliver the service only. eRank takes reasonable steps to ensure that these organizations are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information.

 **Use of your personal information**

For each visitor to reach the site, we expressively collect the following non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to: browser type, version and language, operating system, pages viewed while browsing the Site, page access times, and referring website address. This collected information is used solely internally for the purpose of gauging visitor traffic, monitoring traffic, reviewing trends, and delivering personalized content to you while you are at this Site.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will use for these new policies only. Data collected from the time of the policy change forward will adhere to our updated practices.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

eRank reserves the right to make amendments to this Privacy Policy at any time. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, or concerns about its use or implementation, you should not access or use the Site.

 **Accessing Your Personal Information**

You have a right to access your personal information, subject to exceptions allowed by law. If you would like to do so, please let us know. You may be required to put your request in writing for security reasons and you will be required to provide information sufficient to identify yourself and to document the nature of your request. eRank reserves the right to charge a fee for searching, and providing access to, your information on a per request basis.  Feel free to contact our site administrator for additional details. 

**Right of Removal**

All users have the ability to delete their eRank account whenever they deem it necessary. Deletion will remove their account from our systems, including their personal data such as their name, email address, their sales, feedback and any other data they granted us permission to access when they signed up. Some usage data will be kept in logs for analysis and performance metrics as well as periodic safety and security audits; and, we will keep a record of any payments they made to us for tax reasons. 

**Contacting us**

eRank welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and would like further information, please contact us by e-mail: privacy@erank.com

 **Third parties used**

Google Analytics: used to collect usage statistics for the site. The usage data helps eRank improve the quality of service offered to users.

 **Data we gather from Etsy**

By connecting your Etsy account to eRank, eRank will have permission to do the following on your behalf:

    • Connect to your account and know your member name   
    • Know your email address   
    • See your inactive and expired listings   
    • See your Etsy profile data   
    • See your sales and purchases   
    • See your feedback

This information is used by eRank to provide you with tools and features to help you analyze your shop and spot opportunities to help you grow your business.

 **Updated 6 May 2019.**
